The property of this devil fruit grant the user body the properties of the rubber originally fruit called the Hitohitonomi Nikain classified as a mythical zone fruit type
that allows one to transform into the legendary sun god Nikain, gain his property attributes before being renamed and reclassified by the world government to hide the truth
users body permanently adopt the properties of rubber and they can stretch
their body can stretch bend bounce inflate into it additionally they become almost completely immune to lightning and blunt damage such as blunt
open cannonballs even bullets all of which bounce straight them off
the most ridiculous power in the world the gum gum fruit
zone mythical zone awakened canon
by the simple cyber satyam yado close it
recording for 50 seconds
whisper model loaded loading whisper model